Now we can unzip the file.
现在 我们可以解压文件
We'll do that using Python zip file library.
通过 Python 解压文件库进行解压
Using code to make our wrangling work as reproduceable as possible,
使用代码来做整理工作且可重复操作
as opposed to using an external program or clicking and unzipping the file.
这与使用外部程序或点击解压文件正好相反
So we import the zip file library in this cell,
于是我们将 zip 文件库导入单元格中
then process that cell using shift and enter.
然后按下 “Shift” 和 “Enter”
At this point, we should open up
这个时候 我们应该打开
the zip file library documentation to
zip 文件库文档
figure out how to read the contents of the zip file.
找到读取 zip 文件内容的方法
You can briefly scan through it here, but it's kind of dense.
你可以简略浏览这里 内容有些密集
So I like to use our browsers find
我想使用浏览器的查找功能 即 Command+F 或 Control+F
feature which is command+F or control+F depending on your operating system.
这取决于你的操作系统
Let's look for read.
我们来找找读取功能
We want to read the contents of our zip file.
我们需要读取 zip 文件内容
Okay. Class zipfile.ZipFile, the class for reading and writing zip files.
好的 Class zipfile.ZipFile 是 zip 文件的读写类别
Then it directs us down here, ZipFile Objects.
然后我们转到这里 “ZipFile 对象”
If you're not an expert in Python classes, don't worry.
如果你对 Python 类别不熟 别担心
This just means we can type zipfile.ZipFile with some parameters,
这意味着我们可以给 zipfile.ZipFile 设置一些参数
together called the constructor,
合称“创建者”
to create something called an object
创建一个“对象”
that has special coding abilities also known as methods.
该对象具有特殊的编码能力 也称为“方法”
Okay. If you read through here a little,
好的 如果你通读此处文字
notice that it says the mode parameter should be 'r' to read an existing file.
会注意到 Mode 参数应该为 “r” 以读取当前文件
That's what we want to do.
这正是我们想做的
If we scroll even further we see,
继续向下滚动会看到
"ZipFile is also a context manager and therefore supports the with statement."
“ZipFile 也是一个上下文管理器 因此支持 With 语句”
Context managers are very popular for reading files.
上下文管理器是读取文件的常用功能之一
The act of opening a file,
读写文件时
which we need to do in reading and writing files,
我们需要打开一个文件
consumes a resource on your computer.
这个动作会消耗电脑上的资源
And if we forget to close the file,
如果我们忘记关闭文件
we can get in trouble with error messages or crashes.
我们可能会遇到错误消息或系统崩溃
Context managers make sure all files we open are closed,
上下文管理器可确保关闭所有打开的文件
and all resources we use are properly cleaned up.
并恰当地清理我们使用的所有资源
Okay. So we can actually just copy and paste this code here into our Jupyter Notebook,
好的 我将这个代码复制、粘贴至 Jupyter Notebook 中
but you shouldn't copy and paste it, now and in the future.
但是现在或过后还不能复制、粘贴
Wherever possible, it's best to type out the code.
只要可能 最好用键盘打出代码
It will help you learn, but for the sake of time,
这样做有助于你的学习 但为了节省时间
I'll take a shortcut here and copy and paste.
我先复制和粘贴
We actually need one more thing here,
我们实际还需要一样东西
zipfile.ZipFile to make this code work.
zipfile.ZipFile 这样才能让代码生效
Okay, so we don't want to write to a zip file though
好的 我们不需要使用 ‘w’ 命令 即这里的 write 方法
with this 'w' and this write method here.
来写入 zip 文件
We want to extract or read the files within our zip file.
我们想在 zip 文件内提取或读取文件
A quick Google search directed me to this method within the zip file documentation.
使用 Google 快速搜索让我找到了这个方法
Extractall, which doesn't need any parameters as you can see here,
可以看到 Extractall 不需要任何参数
default none, default none, default none.
三项皆默认为无
In contrast to the Write method which I'll delete right now.
它与 write 方法相反 我马上会删掉这个 write 方法
Okay, so we'll change our code to myzip.extractall with no parameters.
好的 我们将代码更改为无需任何参数的 myzip.extractall
And all that's left to do now is change these two parameters, file and mode.
现在要做的是改变这两个参数 即 file 和 mode
File is the name of the zip file and mode is what we want to do with the file,
file 是 zip 文件的名称 而 mode 是我们想用这个文件做什么
like read or write to it.
比如读取或写入
The zip file we want to open should be in
我们要打开的 zip 文件应与 Jupyter Notebook
the same directory as your Jupyter Notebook at this point.
位于相同目录下
Go ahead and change those parameters.
我们继续改变这些参数